http://www.kettering.edu/give/privacy-policy

History of the Presidency
Stanley R. Liberty (2005-2011)
James E.A. John (1991-2005)
William B. Cottingham (1976-1991)
Harold P. “Dusty” Rodes (1960-1976)
Guy R. Cowing (1950-1960)
Albert J. Sobey, Founder (1919-1950)
Piracy Policy
Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.
Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.
Collection of Information
We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our donors. This information is used to process your gift as well as update our database.
Distribution of Information
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.
Privacy Contact Information
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:
By e-mail: sseamon@kettering.edu
By Phone: (810) 762-9763
We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted. All donations are final.
Terms & Conditions
You, (donor), are responsible for the accuracy of the information supplied by you to Kettering University. In order to make donations online using the payment methods displayed on this website,(e.g., VISA, Mastercard, etc.), you must be 18 years of age or older. By using this website’s payment method, you confirm that you possess the legal authority to instruct Kettering University or its authorized vendors to collect your donation. Billing to your credit card occurs at the time of donation or shortly thereafter. By submitting your information, you authorize Kettering University to charge the credit card provided by you for any donation made on this site.
Give To Kettering
Planned Giving
Corporate & Foundation Giving
